i don't know about all of you but i
cannot stand waking up in the morning
after a long weightlifting session and
hardly being able to move relieving that
soreness is crucial in my opinion and
percussive massage guns offer you the
ability to do that at nearly any given
moment of the day i've been using the
hyperis hypervolt 2 for a couple of
weeks now so today i'm going to break
down my findings for y'all
what's up everybody it's jake back in
the barbing garage gym with another
review ready to go for y'all this time
i've got the hyperis hypervolt 2. in
this review i'm going to tell you
everything you need to know about this
massage gun from the price and the
features some pros and cons you might
run into and of course who should or
maybe should not buy this massage gun
before i get started with any of that
though i have to let you know we've
reviewed a good amount of massage guns
on varbin.com so if you want to browse
our best list just go and search barbin
best massage guns and you can find out
for yourself which ones we like the best
all right now before i really dig into
what i like about this massage gun if
you aren't familiar with what a
percussive massage is basically it's a
combination of rapid and repetitive
pressure mixed in with vibrational
therapy so what's going to happen is the
head of the massage gun is going to move
quickly and apply enough force mixed in
with that vibrational therapy to relieve
any stiffness you may have in your soft
tissue okay so what do i like about the
hyperis hypervolt ii well i really like
how it comes with five different
attachments for you to use there's a lot
of versatility here every single one is
meant for a specific purpose but i'll
talk about all that in just a minute the
companion app is a really great tool it
provides guided sessions on how to
properly use this massage gun and i
really like the shape of the handle it's
shaped like an oval it's going to allow
you to get a really solid grip plus it's
wrapped in rubber which is going to
assist your grip even more and it only
weighs 1.8 pounds so you're not going to
get too tired as you're using it and
plus it's not going to be too heavy if
you put it in your bag
[Music]
okay so what about those potential cons
you might run into with the hypervolt
too let's talk about the speed settings
first you only have three to work with
it's not a whole lot of variety there
there's some other massage guns out
there that have five some even have more
than five
now in terms of their slowest speed
setting i personally would like to have
something a little bit slower than
what's available sometimes i get really
sore and this can actually kind of hurt
a little bit so it would be nice if
there was something just a tick slower
than what's available
okay so including shipping the hypervolt
2 is listed right around 300 and you can
buy it directly from the hypers website
or do what we did and buy it through
rogue now 300
is a lot of money for a massage gun
don't get me wrong but when you compare
this price to going to see a massage
therapist every so often this is
eventually gonna pay for itself
okay so let's take a second to talk
about the companion app that hypers has
to offer probably my favorite feature to
be honest with you because it shows you
guided sessions on how to properly
relieve that soreness in any specific
muscle group that you may need it for so
what you're going to do is you're going
to set up your profile it's going to ask
you to fill out what activities you
participate in i mean this ranges from
running to working out even just
traveling sitting in an office all day
there's an option for basically every
single activity that you may participate
in and the point of doing that is the
app's going to provide you with specific
routines for what you filled out that
way you can relieve the stress and the
tension that you may have there's also a
routines tab which is really helpful so
let's say you have some tight hips or
maybe some neck tension from craning
over a computer all day there's gonna be
specific routines for anything you may
need it's gonna allow you to really
unlock those specific areas it was a
little weird though in my opinion that
there's not some routines for specific
muscle groups such as your pecs and your
lats even your abs and a couple other
ones so
that is probably you know in the works
of happening but as of right this moment
today it's not available
[Music]
okay so let's break down the build with
the hypervolt ii let's talk about the
handle first
it's about six inches in diameter and
it's shaped like an oval so it's going
to give you a really solid grip in my
opinion it fits really solid in your
hands plus it's wrapped in rubber it's
gonna assist you even more it's about
nine and a half inches tall and without
an attachment here it's about six and a
half inches from front to back so i'd
say about seven seven and a half inches
maybe with this attachment on there now
three of the attachments are made from a
hard plastic this ball right here though
is a little foamy to me in my opinion
it's going to be really nice for some
sensitive areas but especially this
cushion attachment
it's really cushiony as you may assume
and this is really going to be the one
you want to go to
if you're wanting to use it on your hand
your wrist anything around the neck
that's going to be the go-to that's
definitely my favorite attachment that's
available here and once again this only
weighs 1.8 pounds so you're really not
going to get too fatigued as you're
using it
[Music]
all right now in terms of features i
want to focus on the attachments first
and foremost as you see you do have five
different ones for you to use it's a lot
of versatility here so the one i have
attached right here is that flat head
it's gonna be great for any large muscle
groups this cushion right here once
again it's pretty cushiony it's gonna be
great for your wrist anything around
your neck anything really super
sensitive that's what you're gonna gonna
wanna go with the bolt attachment is
gonna be great for pinpoint therapy and
your glutes and hammies stuff like that
this
ball right here that's going to be great
for just overall usage any large muscle
groups and this fork attachment is going
to be great for any longer muscles such
as your forearms your biceps your calves
stuff like that and actually i think
this would be really nice on either side
of your spine as well you also get this
nice little bag right here for you to
store all of your attachments in keep
everything you know nice and clutter
free if you plan on traveling overseas
hypers has your back you do in fact have
three different outlet attachments right
here depending on which part of the
world you're traveling to so that's
pretty nice as well okay so the power
button on the back of your hypervolt 2
is actually going to double as a speed
changer so once you turn this on just
simply tap the button and it will cycle
through your speed settings pretty
easily done you also have three
different led lights right here that are
going to signal what speed you're on
it's also a little light right here it's
going to flash blue that's going to
signal your bluetooth and show you you
are in fact connected to your phone now
you also are going to have a ring down
here i'll go ahead and turn this on for
you it takes about two and a half
seconds or so for it to come on when
it's green that means your battery is
fully charged over time this color is
going to change to yellow and orangish
yellow and then eventually red until
your battery has died now this is
designed to last for right around three
hours but the battery life could change
obviously depending on what speed
setting you have it on and as well as
how much pressure you're putting onto
your body now if it were to die that's
bound to happen eventually it's gonna
take you right around three hours for it
to charge which really isn't that bad in
the grand scheme of things
all right so let's do a quick walk
around with the hypervolt 2 i'm going to
start with how to turn it on i showed
you earlier i'm going to show you again
power button right here just simply
press and hold for a couple of seconds
that's going to come on when it's fully
charged it'll be green just like this as
the battery starts to die it'll be
yellow then orange just yellow and then
red until it's dead now the power button
right here it's going to double as your
speed changer as i said earlier you
press it it comes on you see we're on
that lowest setting
cycle through all three
and then press it again to turn the
motor off really easy to do
just press and hold again for a couple
seconds and that's going to turn it off
now if you want to change your
attachments that's really easy to do
just simply pull out
grab whichever one you want
push nice and solid in there it's not
going to move
now
if this does die
your charging port is located underneath
and if you go overseas you know you do
have three different attachments right
here for you to use for your outlet
ignore my remote right here it's for my
fan it gets a little hot in here as i've
told you all before so sometimes i have
to mess with that now once you decide
what part of your body that you want to
work on you know go to that companion
app find the exact region of your body
and just simply you know cut it on
and then sit here and use it for about
no more than two minutes now a lot of
people don't know this but if you were
to use this for more than two minutes in
a specific area you actually run the
risk of causing yourself more injury and
you know the purpose of this is to
prevent injury and to recover
not to hurt yourself
[Music]
all right now who should purchase the
hyperis hypervolt 2 well i really think
this is a great tool for anybody who
wants to take the best care possible of
their body yes it is an expensive tool
but if you incorporate it into your
daily routine then i definitely think
the benefits are going to make it worth
that price tag if you're looking for
your massage gun to be as versatile
really as you could imagine for it to be
i think you're really going to enjoy the
five different attachments that you have
here they're all meant for a specific
purpose and they're going to allow you
to unlock every single muscle group in
your body
and lastly you know if you're somebody
who's looking for a massage gun but you
don't really know how to use one the
right way well the companion app is
going to be your best friend
all you have to do is select which
muscle group that you want to focus on
and it's going to provide you with
routines for you to unlock your body and
relieve that soreness
all right now what about the people who
might not want to purchase the hypervolt
2 well honestly if you don't plan on
incorporating massage therapy into your
daily routine then i'd suggest looking
for a cheaper alternative you know this
is a premium product available at a
premium price tag so it's definitely
going to be better suited for somebody
who does incorporate it into their daily
routine
if you want your massage gun to feature
a slower speed setting you're definitely
going to want to keep looking there's
other ones out there that are a little
bit slower than what the slowest speed
setting is with the hyper bolt 2 but
those also may not be as effective
overall and lastly
some people just don't really care for
massage guns in that case you don't
really have any reason to buy one of
these because i'm sure you would rather
go and see a massage therapist to work
out any kinks that you may have
that's all i have for y'all today over
the hyperis hypervolt 2 this is a great
product for anyone who is very serious
about their recovery the five different
attachments add a lot of versatility to
this massage gun and are going to allow
you to really focus on every single
portion of your body the speed settings
may not be ideal for every single person
out there now don't get me wrong they're
definitely effective they just might be
a little too rough for any super sore
muscles and sensitive areas
as always keep your eyes peeled for my
next review but for now head over to
barbin.com and you can read more about
this massage gun just search barbind
hyperis hypervolt 2 review and you can
read about everything i talked about
here today i'll see you all next time
[Music]
you